（忆往昔）
你知道小卡做了什么
You know what Cass did?
你弟弟脑子里那道屏障没了
The dam inside your brother's head is gone,
所有地狱的记忆都倾巢而出
and all hell's spilling loose.
每当我一闭眼 路西法就冲我大喊大叫
Every time I close my eyes, Lucifer is yelling into my head.
早安 越南
Good morning, Vietnam!
你知道他并不是真的…
You know he's not actually…
对 我知道
Yeah. No, I know that.
这话跟我脑袋里的音量控制开关说吧
Try telling that to the volume control inside my brain.
你没再试试掐伤口那招
Did you try the hand thing?
大哥哥也许已经死了
Big brother's probably dead.
闭嘴
Shut up.
他对我说「闭嘴」了
He said "shut up" to me.
你让我进去了
You let me in.
你想要我 搭档
You wanted me, partner.
我确信我搞定你了 铺友
I do believe I've got you, bunk buddy.
萨姆 你可不能睡
No nap for you, Sammy.
（如今）
混蛋
Dick!
哥们
Dude.
你离我远点
Get the hell away from me.
你会说英语吗
You speak friggin' English?
滚开
Go away!
没关系
It's okay.
没人追我
No one's after me.
- 那你跑什么 - 就…
- Why are you running up in here like that? - Just…
别管我就好
Just leave me alone.
你磕什么药了
What the hell did you take, anyway?
什么也没磕
Nothing.
得了吧
Shut up.
不 他说的是实话
No, he's telling the truth.
上瓶啤酒的劲早就过了
Burned through that last beer hours ago.
大约就在迪恩睡过去的时候
Right about the time Dean passed out.
来嘛 萨姆 告诉这个好心的瘾君子
Come on, Sam. Tell the nice tweaker.
要不是魔王对你寸步不离
You'd be sleeping by now if the devil would just.
你现在早睡着了
leave you alone for five seconds.
讨厌的撒旦
Stupid Satan.
一路追你到…
Chasing you all the way to…
这是哪儿啊
Where the hell are we?
我只是需要休息
I just need some rest.
萨姆
Hey. Sam.
掐掐手上的疤啊
Try the hand scar.
你几天没睡觉了
How many days you been up, anyway?
四天
Four.
等等 收回那句话
Oh. Wait. Scratch that.
是五天
Five.
等等 先别走 等等
Hey, hold up! Wait! Hold up!
你想嗨吗 我可以给你点药
You want to knock out? I can knock you out.
∮ 祝你早安 ∮
∮ Good morning to you ∮
∮ 崭新的一天已降临 ∮
∮ Our day is beginning ∮
∮ 祝你早安 ∮
∮ So good morning to you ∮
我还以为你喜欢听我唱歌呢
I thought you liked my singing!
嗑药
Pills?
你知道你这是给自己帮倒忙吧
You do get that you're just bringing free drugs to the party, right?
我活在你脑袋里 萨姆
I am inside you, Sam.
嗨 萨姆
Hey. Sam.
正常人类连续不睡觉的
What's the longest a normal human being.
最高纪录是多久
has ever gone without sleep?
十一天
11 days.
你一直想做正常人 萨姆
You always wanted to be normal, Sam!
如果你是正常人 那一周内就死翘翘了
If you are, you'll be dead in a week!
[邪恶力量 第7季第17集]
先生 没有预约
Okay, sir? You can't just barge in here.
- 你不能擅自闯进来 - 他们让我找卡丁斯基
- without an appointment! - They said, "Talk to Kadinsky."
你是卡丁斯基吗
You Kadinsky?
- 你需要先预约 - 那就帮我安排啊
- You need to be scheduled! - Well, then, schedule me!
他出了车祸
He was in a car crash.
我凭什么不能见他
Why the hell can't I see him?
你是萨姆·史密斯的哥哥吗
You're Sam Smith's brother.
对 怎么回事啊
Yeah, what's going on?
没关系 谢谢你 真没事
I-it's fine. Thank you. Really.
萨姆住院了
Sam was admitted.
他肋骨骨折 还有撕裂伤
He was treated for a broken rib and lacerations.
- 情况不算太糟 还有呢 - 还有
- Okay. That's not too bad. And? - And…
他在我们封闭精神科住院
He's on our locked psychiatric floor.
他虽然是有点问题…
I mean, he's had some trouble…
那么说你知道萨姆正在经受
So you're aware that Sam is experiencing.
精神病发作的折磨
a full-blown psychotic episode?
精神病
Psychotic?
得了吧 我弟弟…
Come on. I mean, the guy's…
我弟弟又不是什么精神病患者
It's not like the guy's freakin' Norman Bates.
是啊 他肯定不是
No, I'm sure he isn't.
我们要进一步确定他目前的症状
We need to determine whether his state.
是否由失眠引起
was brought on by the insomnia.
还是说失眠只是他精神病的一种症状
or whether the insomnia is a symptom of his condition.
明白吗 以便我们制定治疗计划
Do you understand? So that we can figure out how to treat him.
我只知道他是最近才开始失眠的
Well, all I can say is that the sleep thing is kind of new.
是这样
Right.
我们已给他注射了最大安全剂量的镇定剂
We've pumped him about as full of sedatives as we safely can.
可目前他还是清醒的
So far, he won't go under.
我真没见过这种情况
I've never seen anything like it.
（高度戒备区）
我说啊
I'm just sayin'.
你没灵魂那会儿
Back when you had no soul…
你从来用不着睡觉
You never had to sleep.
无助先生来啦
Ah, Mr. Helpless.
带酒来没
Pull up a six-pack, buddy.
感觉怎么样
How are you feeling?
我大概参加不了终极格斗大赛了
Maybe you should cancel my UFC fight.
很好 保持这种幽默感 萨姆
Yeah. Keep that sense of humor, Sam.
能帮你渡过难关
It'll get you through this.
萨姆 我会找医生帮你治病
Sam, I'm gonna find you help.
你好像不太信服啊
Now, that sounded a little cynical.
我觉得没人能帮上我 迪恩
I don't think it's out there, Dean.
那可不一定
We don't know that.
咱们心里最清楚不过了
We know better than most.
都是些骗人的把戏
It's all snake oil.
咱们上次碰到的信仰治疗师
Last faith healer we hooked up with.
使咒抓了个死神给她干活 记得吗
had a reaper on a leash. Remember?
是啊
Yeah…
萨姆 我记得
Sam, I remember.
我的意思是…
I'm just saying…
什么
What?
你不想让我帮你吗
That you don't want my help?
不 我的意思是
No, I'm just saying.
你没必要这么折磨自己
don't do this to yourself.
萨姆 如果我找不到人帮你
Sam, if I don't find something …
我就会死
Then I'll die.
你们说得人家都郁闷了
Oh, you're upsetting me.
- 迪恩 你知道这是迟早的事 - 不
- Dean, we knew this was coming. - No.
- 你帮我找回灵魂的时候就知道 - 不
- When you put my soul back. - No.
小卡警告过你会发生什么…
Cass warned you about all the crap it would …
小卡去死吧
Screw Cass!
你别这么淡定好不好
Quit being Dali Frickin' Yoda about this, okay?
有点火气行不行
Get pissed!
我太累了
I'm too tired.
把人的灵魂跟路西法关一起就会变成这样
This is what happens when you throw a soul into Lucifer's dog bowl.
你还真以为会有救吗
When you think there's just gonna be some cure out there?
你们俩挺感伤的啊
Oh, you guys are having a moment.
我是鲍比·辛格的一个朋友
I'm a friend of Bobby Singer's.
我想查些信息
I'm looking for some info.
如果你能帮忙 请回电
If you could, uh, call me back.
785-555-0128
785-555-0128.
谢谢
Thanks.
很抱歉打扰你了
I am so sorry to have bothered you.
自恋型人格障碍
Narcissistic personality disorder.
说真的 我可能有这条
Okay, now, this one I could have.
该吃药了 萨姆
Time for meds, Sam.
设定不现实的目标 有这条
Sets unrealistic goals. Check.
但是「不能和他人保持健康的关系」
But "trouble keeping healthy relationships?"
这一条我不是很确定 你有什么想法
Not so sure about that one. Thoughts?
好吧 谢谢
Yeah. Thanks.
（麦基的标本公司）
你好 我是迪恩
Yeah, hi. Uh… my name's Dean.
我是鲍比·辛格的一个朋友
I'm a friend of Bobby Singer's.
我想查些信息
I'm, uh, looking for some info.
如果你能帮我请回电7855550128
If you could call me back at 785-555-0128.
谢谢
Thanks.
萨姆 今天感觉怎么样
Sam, how are we feeling today?
用一到十级来形容你肋骨的疼痛
Rib pain … scale of 1 to 10?
不那么疼了
It's … it's not bad.
三级吧
3.
你用不着撒谎的 萨姆
You don't have to lie, Sam.
我…我没有啊
I'm … I'm not.
你在忍受着巨大的痛苦
You've suffered terrible agony.
这么说来你的十级一定难以想象了
I mean, your 10 must be astronomical.
是 我想我比较能忍疼吧
Yeah. I-I guess I have a high threshold.
对
Yeah.
但是最糟的部分是知道没有最疼只有更疼
But the worst is knowing that there's always a new 10.
你在说什么
What are you talking about?
我说的是我今天为你准备的
Well, I'm talking about the truly elegant torture.
真正的痛苦的折磨 萨姆
I have prepared for you today, Sam.
离我远点
Just stay the hell away from me.
但是咱们刚才聊得多好啊
But it's … it's so nice chatting.
萨姆 你不理我真让我伤心啊
Sam, I hate these one-sided conversations.
来吧 伙计 来单挑
Come on, buddy. Engage.
萨姆
Sam?
你
You…
和我
me…
关在这
locked ward.
难道只有我感觉这就像个笼子吗
Is it me, or is this just like the cage?
我是迪恩
This is Dean.
我是麦基 给你回电话了
MacKey. Calling you back.
鲍比的事我很难过
Hey. Real sorry about Bobby.
我也是
Yeah, me too.
你打电话说的事
Look, what you called about …
我可能有对你有用的信息
I might have something for you.
有个家伙 叫伊曼纽尔
There's this guy. He goes by "Emanuel."
他到处走
He kind of roams.
几个月前开始听说他的
First started hearing about him a couple of months back.
他能治愈伤者 包括那些疯子
Now, he was healing the sick, curing the crazy.
不用说 我觉得这家伙肯定有蹊跷
Naturally, I think something in the milk ain't clean.
于是打算找到他 让他收摊滚蛋
Find this sucker, punch his clock.
- 明白吗 - 明白
- Right? - Right.
听说想找他最好的办法就是通过他妻子
Heard the best way to get to him is through his wife,
她叫达芙妮 在科罗拉多州
Daphne, out in Colorado.
所以我就去了
So, I go.
告诉她我快瞎了 这倒是真的
Tell her I'm going blind. It's true.
我的右眼快完了
My right eye's burnt out.
她说 「你回家吧 他会去的」
She says, "Go home. He'll come."
于是我就回家了
So, I go.
我布置了所有能找到的陷阱和测试
I set every trap, every test in the book.
是我也会这么干的
That's what I would have done.
伊曼纽尔出现了
Emanuel shows.
他通过了所有陷阱和测试
He passes every one.
这家伙很正常
There ain't nothing weird about this guy,
不过…
except…
他真有两下子
he's the real deal.
你什么意思
What do you mean?
他碰了我一下
He touched me,
我的眼睛就好了
and my eye was fixed.
我也觉得这有点不可思议
Look, I don't believe in much that don't suck your blood,
但我不确定也不会打给你
but I wouldn't call you on a maybe.
「我头疼死了
"Oh, my head hurts.
停下来吧「
Make it stop!"
你好
Hello?
你想不想要这个
You want this or not?
我昨天见过你
I saw you yesterday.
你好像不怎么喜欢这的饭菜
You didn't look too happy with your in-flight meal.
谢谢
Thanks. Uh…
我是玛琳 不用谢
Marin. No problem.
你是萨姆 对吗
Sam. Right?
「对
"That's it.
我是萨姆「
I'm Sam."
「我是萨姆 你好」
"I'm Sam. Hi."
你好 这是达芙妮·艾伦的家吗
Hi. Uh, is this, uh, Daphne Allen's house?
我是来找伊曼纽尔的
I'm looking for Emanuel.
我就是
Well, you found him.
达芙妮在睡觉
Daphne's resting,
我们出来说行吗
if you don't mind.
没事
Oh, yeah, sure.
我希望你能…
So, I was hoping…
你想说什么啊 迪恩
You were saying, Dean?
我要是你就三思
You know, I'd think twice.
你不知道你老大放话说不能碰我们吗
Or don't you know that your boss issued a hands-off memo?
得了吧
Please.
你最近为他做过什么
What have you done for him lately?
你把罗曼的头砍下来了 没有吧
Roman's head on a plate? No?
不管伊曼纽尔是什么 克劳力肯定想要他
Whatever Emanuel is, Crowley's gonna want him …
相对来说他目前肯定没那么稀罕你
a lot more than he wants you these days.
所以…
So…
怎么回事
What was that?
那怪物伤了你
That creature hurt you.
我没事
I'm okay.
但是 伊曼纽尔
But, Emanuel…
他们是冲你来的
they were looking for you.
没事的
It's okay.
我是伊曼纽尔
I'm Emanuel.
迪恩 我是迪恩
Dean. I'm…Dean.
谢谢你保护我妻子
Thank you for protecting my wife.
你妻子 对
Your wife. Right.
我看见他的脸了
I saw his face.
他真正的面容
His real face.
他是个恶魔
He was a demon.
人间居然出了一个恶魔
A demon walked the Earth.
不止一个
Demons.
有一大群恶魔呢
Whackloads of them.
你难道不知道
You don't know about…
你看到了恶魔的真身
You saw the demon's true face.
伊曼纽尔天赋秉异
Emanuel has very special gifts.
是啊 我 我听说过
Yeah. I-I've heard that about…
伊曼纽尔
Emanuel.
你能治愈人们
That you can heal people up.
我似乎在一定程度上能帮助别人
I seem to be able to help to a certain degree.
你遇到了什么问题
What's your issue?
是我弟弟
My brother.
说实在的 你比我想的要坚强多了
You know, you're actually keeping it together better than I thought.
就像 身负重压 却还能坚持得住
Kind of…the way someone pinned under a bus keeps it together.
这都不是真的
None of this is real.
不过 你知道什么才是最糟的吗
And yet… you know what really sucks?
这无关紧要
It doesn't really matter.
因为我赢了
Because I won.
你的疯狂赢了
Your madness won.
看看你吧
I mean, look at you.
难以相信
It's hard to believe.
你就是那个一度拯救世界的家伙
you were the guy that saved the world once.
小萨姆
Mmm! Sammy.
今天吃什么 还吃蛆
What'll be today? Maggots again,
或是绦虫
or, uh, tapeworm?
谢谢
Thanks.
不客气
Yeah, no problem.
你还好吗
How are you doing?
好一点了
Uh…little better.
那个叫玛琳的女孩
That girl, uh, Marin…
听着 这话我真的不该讲
Look, I'm not really supposed to talk about it.
这么说吧 她不像你
Let's just say, unlike you,
她可不是因意外事故入院的
she didn't get here 'cause of no accident.
达芙妮
So, Daphne …
是 你的妻子
is that, uh, your wife?
她找到了我 并照顾我
She found me and cared for me.
什么意思
Meaning?
是个 奇怪的故事 你可能不会喜欢
Oh, it's a…strange story. You may not like it.
相信我 我会的
Believe me, I will.
几个月前 她到河边远足
A few months ago, she was hiking by the river,
我徘徊到她面前
and I wandered into her path,
浑身湿透 迷迷糊糊 还 一丝不挂
drenched and confused, and…unclothed.
我失忆了
I had no memory.
她说
She said…
上帝希望她找到我
God wanted her to find me.
那是谁给你取名伊曼纽尔
So who named you Emanuel?
在快活宝贝起名网上找到的
Bouncybabynames.com.
挺适合你的
Well, it's working for you.
不知道自己是谁一定很奇怪
Must be weird not knowing who you are.
这就是我的生活
Well, it's my life.
而且是很棒的生活
And it's a good life.
好吧 如果你是个
Yeah, well, what if you were some kind of…
比如说 是个坏蛋怎么办
I don't know…bad guy?
我并不感觉自己是坏人
Oh, I… don't feel like a bad person.
天呐 你还真是铁了心不睡觉了
Man, you must be really determined to wait out nap time.
给你
Here.
等等 和我一起吃吧
Wait. Uh… share this with me.
谢谢
Thanks.
不知道为什么我为自己偷的糖感谢你
I don't know why I'm thanking you for a candy bar I stole.
你来这里多久了
So, how long you been here?
到目前五周了
Five weeks and counting.
我要打破住院记录了
Going for the record.
你为什么入院
How come?
那不重要
It doesn't matter.
你说不重要 却贴着那么多纱布
That's a lot of bandages for "It doesn't matter."
你想听听医生的说法吗
You want the doctor answer?
精神压抑导致产生轻生的想法
I'm psychotically depressed to a suicidal ideation.
那真实情况是什么
And the not doctor answer?
我感觉糟透了
I feel like crap.
我只是 想结束它
I just… want it to be over.
什么
What?
结束一切
Everything.
说吧 说我我还年轻 生活充满希望
Come on. Tell me I'm young, and have everything to live for.
我说怎么能让你信服
Why would you believe me?
说的也对
True.
我听说你在这里
I have heard you're here.
因为有些声音让你无法睡觉
because the voices won't let you sleep.
其实只有一个声音
Just one, really.
是谁
Who is it?
比如查理·曼森（杀死大导演波兰斯基家人的凶犯）还是撒旦
Like Charlie Manson or the devil?
差不多
Kind of. Yeah.
我也是
Me too.
我能听到一个声音
I…hear a voice.
这就是你放火的原因吗
Is that why you set the fire?
谁告诉你的
Who told you that?
没人 你脖子上的是烧伤 对吗
No one. T-They're burns, right?
不是我放的火 是他
I didn't set the fire, o… he did!
我都不知道我为什么说这些
You know what? I don't even know why I'm talking.
玛琳 没事的
Marin, it's okay.
怎么没事
No, it's not!
你比我还疯
You are crazier than I am!
查尔斯·曼森告诉你该做什么
Charles Manson tells you what to do.
至少我听到的是自己哥哥的声音
At least it's my own brother …
是你哥哥
It's your brother?
是的
Yes.
这感觉真糟
It sucks…
你死去的哥哥跟你说
when it's your dead brother saying…
让你自杀来陪他
kill yourself to be with him…
否则他就亲自动手
…or he'll do it for you.
你弟弟
So, your brother…
萨姆
Sam.
医生对他的诊断是什么
What's his diagnosis?
其实不是医学病症
Well, it's not exactly medical.
应该没问题
That should be fine.
我能治愈心灵的疾病
I can cure illness of a spiritual origin.
心灵
Spiritual?
好吧
Okay.
有人害他变成了这样
Someone did this to him.
你很生气
You're angry.
是的 那家伙弄坏了我弟弟的脑袋
Well, yeah. Dude broke my brother's head.
这个人背叛了你
He betrayed you, this dude.
他原来是你的朋友吗
He was your friend?
是的 他死了
Yeah, well, he's gone.
是你杀了他吗
Did you kill him?
我感觉到你杀过很多人
I sense that you kill a lot of people.
说实话 我 我不知道他是否死了
Honestly, I-I don't know if he's dead.
我只知道
I just know that this…
这件事糟得不能再糟了
whole thing couldn't be messier.
要知道 我以前总能把这种事放在身后
You know, I used to be able to just shake this stuff off.
不管是什么
You know, whatever it was.
或许需要点时间 但是
It might take me some time, but…
我总是能做到
I always could.
可小卡做的事
What Cass did…
不知为什么 我就是迈不过这个坎
I just can't … I don't know why.
为什么并不重要
Well, it doesn't matter why.
当然重要了
Of course it matters.
不 你不是台机器 迪恩
No. You're not a machine, Dean.
你是个人
You're human.
你朋友叫小卡
Your friend's name was Cass?
名字好怪
That's an odd name.
坐这儿别动 我就出来
Just, uh, sit tight. I'll be right out, okay?
不是吧
Oh, come on.
伊曼纽尔 你个混蛋
Emanuel, you son of a bitch.
伊曼纽尔
Emanuel.
不是他
Yeah, not so much.
梅格
Meg.
迪恩 迪恩 你得好好解释解释
Dean, Dean, Dean. You got some 'splainin' to do.
（停业）
这个伊曼纽尔的事迹传的满天飞啊
Rumors are really starting to fly about this Emanuel fellow.
我是好奇得不得了
My curiosity sure got revved up.
就直说你想干嘛吧 梅格
Just tell me what you want, Meg.
我找到他时 却发现他小鸟依人地跟着你
Imagine my surprise when I track him down,
想想我有多惊讶
and he's snuggled up with you.
而且他长得跟已故的可怜虫卡西迪奥一模一样
And he's the spitting image of poor, dead Castiel.
迪恩 可怜的卡西迪奥都死了
So, Dean, what's poor, dead Castiel.
怎么会出现在外面的那辆破车上
doing in that junker out there?
唱圣诞颂歌
Christmas caroling.
真风趣 他怎么会还活着
Fun. But how's he alive?
据我所知 他扮演上帝 结果爆炸了
Last I heard, he played God, went poof.
我不知道
I don't know.
而且他也不知道 所以你少多嘴
And neither does he, so you got to keep it shut.
是吗
Oh, I do?
他不知道他是小卡
He doesn't know he's Cass.
我知道 我盯了你们几小时了
I know. Been watching you for hours.
我们这么办吧
So here's the deal.
还记得我和克劳力以前的关系不怎么样吗
You might remember Crowley and me were frosty back in the day?
- 现在也没改善 - 那太好了
- Well, times haven't changed. - Good.
你真伤我感情 我可待你不薄 迪恩
That hurts my feelings. I've been good to you, Dean.
你不过是关照自己
No, you've been good to you, sweetheart.
听着
Look.
到目前关于这个云游治疗师的谣言传得还不算远
Right now, rumors of this wandering healer are strictly low-level.
但是死了这么多人 纸包不住火
But body count's getting high enough to change that.
有人开始四处打探 他们闻得到天使的味
Folks start poking, they sniff angel dust.
为了跑去克劳力那儿邀功都能挤死人
Yeah, they start falling all over each other trying to tell Crowley.
想想克劳力要是抓到温良无害的失忆小卡会怎样
Now picture Crowley with his hands on harmless little amnesia Cass.
别误会
Don't get me wrong.
我要杀了那个口蜜腹剑的混蛋
I'm gonna burn that smarmy dick.
姐就要称霸了
My time's coming.
不过我目前孤军奋战 所以说我实力还不够
But right about now, my army-of-one situation is not cutting it.
形势严峻 杀我者有赏
It's cold out here, there's a price on my ass,
所以我需要盟友
and I need friends.
了解
Yeah. I get that.
可我不是你的盟友
But I ain't it.
这你就错了 迪恩
That's where you're wrong, Dean.
我是来帮你的 这样一来我们就是朋友了
'Cause I'm here to help you, and that makes us friends.
帮我
Help, huh?
你是想看看能不能把外面那个温良无害的小卡
You mean see if you can't turn harmless little Cass out there.
变成全能天使大杀器吧
into an angel-sized weapon?
别装得好像你对他没企图似的
Like you're taking him caroling.
再说 你真想不带后援就继续上路吗
And by the way, you really want to keep going with no backup?
我也不信任你
Hey, I don't trust you, either.
但是我用得上伊曼纽尔
But I could really use Emanuel.
而他信任你
And he trusts you.
所以现在我们联手
So for now, it's in everyone's best interests.
对大家都有好处
to hold hands and cross the street together, okay?
我们直接去找萨姆
We go straight to Sam.
不去别处
No detours.
如此甚好
I love it.
对了
And one more thing.
还我刀
My knife.
我们跟气场全开的天使结伴旅行不是更安全吗
You sure we wouldn't be safer traveling with a full-throttle Angel?
我可以让他都记起来
I could jog his memory.
逗你玩呢
Kidding!
谁都不想惹那小可怜难过嘛
We wouldn't want to upset the poor guy.
她的脸 她是
Her face! She's one of …
别紧张 坏蛋还分三六九等呢
It's okay. We come in different flavors.
她是 我朋友
She's, uh…A friend.
我是梅格
Meg.
来精神支持你们
Just here for moral support.
毕竟我们交情老深了
I mean, after all, we go way back.
我是说迪恩和我
Dean and me.
我跟你当然是初次相见
Just met you, of course.
但我想我们也会成为好朋友的
I think we're gonna be good friends, too.
好了 我们走吧
All right. Can we go?
玛琳 玛琳 等等
Marin. Marin, hey. Hold on.
抱歉 惹你难过了
Um…I'm sorry I upset you.
没事
It's okay.
能问你点事吗
Can I ask you something?
什么事
About?
火灾的事
The fire.
听着 你虽是好意 但你根本不知道
Look. You mean well, but you have no idea …
你说不是你点的火
You said you didn't start it.
我相信你
I believe you.
玛琳 我能帮你
I can help you, Marin,
让他不能再伤害你
before he tries to hurt you again.
你气色更差了
You're worse.
你的器官需要休息
Your organs need sleep, you know.
这样下去 你的头发和指甲会脱落
Your hair and nails are gonna fall out,
肾脏会停止工作
and your kidneys are gonna shut down.
我在电影里看过
I saw it in a movie.
抱歉
Sorry.
你哥哥
So, um, your brother …
他什么时候死的
when did he pass?
去年
Uh, last year.
你能看到他吗
Do you see him?
那么
So…
他只是跟他说话
he just talks to you.
但起初并没出事
But at first it wasn't so bad.
你一定很想他
You must have missed him.
你是在家听到他说话的吗
Did you just hear him at the house?
在这儿也能
Here too.
只要我一个人的时候
Whenever I'm alone.
我总是能感到他靠近 因为我会觉得冷
I can always tell he's coming because I get these chills.
你觉得冷
You feel cold.
对
Yeah.
你说得对
I mean, you're right.
最开始…
At first it's like…
我知道自己疯了 但是
I knew I was crazy, but…
我不在乎
I didn't really care.
我真的很想念他
I did miss him.
但后来…
But then…
他开始说他很寂寞
He started saying he was lonely.
他开始发火
And he started to get mad.
有一天他开始尖叫
And one day he started yelling,
我想逃走 但门已经被锁上了
and I tried to run but the door was locked.
等我转过身 整个房间都着火了
And when I turned around, the whole room was on fire.
我差点就死在里面了
I barely got out.
你怎么帮得了我
How can you help me?
我能让你哥哥安息
I can put your brother to rest.
他…
He's, um…
他被困在这里了
He's stuck here.
你是说真的吗 就是说
For real? Like …
他变成鬼了
Like he's a ghost.
我凭什么相信你
Why should I trust you?
因为你别无选择
Because it's your only shot.
好吧
Okay.
很好
那你哥哥 是火葬还是土葬
So, your brother … was he cremated? Buried?
火葬
We cremated him.
你还留着他的东西吗
And do you have anything of his?
这个 他亲手为我做的
This. He made it for me.
当时他手还伤着呢
With a busted hand, too.
是射箭的时候把手割伤了
Sliced it open doing stupid archery.
上面还有他的血
He bled on it?
可能吧
Probably.
很好 很好
Good. That's … that's good.
好什么
Why is that good?
还有个问题
One more question.
你能不能找个打火机来
Is there any chance in hell you got a lighter?
安静得让我不舒服
This silence is very uncomfortable.
有什么要告诉我的吗
Is there something I should know?
我不知道
I don't know.
迪恩
Dean?
没有
No.
梅格就有这气场
Meg has that effect.
让人很不爽 晓得吧
Awkward. You know?
这一定让你很不便吧
That must be difficult for you.
迪恩在说笑呢 伊曼纽尔
Dean's making a joke, Emanuel.
不错
Nice.
你在哪儿找到的
Where'd you score that?
从马科斯的口袋里取出来的
Grabbed it out of Marcus' pocket.
我关在这里倒成了犯罪高手
Being locked up is really turning me into a decent criminal.
我们得画个圈出来
We're laying down a circle.
帮我打开
Help me open these, okay?
你得自己来搞定这个
You're gonna have to do this on your own.
没事没事 我只是有点…
It's okay. I'm okay. I'm just having a little…
- 药物反应 - 眼花了
- Brown acid moment… - Dizzy thing.
会没事的
It'll pass.
必须的 你死了就没事了
Definitely. When your heart stops.
很好 现在我们
Great. Now, um…
跟我一起站在圈内
Stay with me in the circle.
不管发生什么
No matter what.
不管发生什么情况 好吗
No matter what happens, okay?
会发生什么
What's gonna happen?
把那个手链给我
Give me the bracelet.
玛琳 求你别这么做
Marin, don't do this. Please.
玛琳 把手链给我
Marin, give me the bracelet.
对不起 我没办法
I'm so sorry. I have to.
不
Noooo!
你得离开了
Y-you got to go.
快走
Go.
谢谢你
Thank you.
萨姆 现在感觉怎样
Sam? How you feeling now?
他的灵魂有损伤 医生
His soul is broken, Doc.
你给开点药吗
Can you give him a pill?
我没法再对你用药了
I can't give you any more medication.
否则很可能会过量
The potential for overdose is too great.
我们得考虑用手术解决了
We need to talk about surgical solutions.
手术
Surgical?
额叶切除术
Ooh. Lobotomy?
没事 不是额叶切除术
It's okay. We're not talking lobotomy here.
真烦
Darn.
萨姆
Sam.
听得见吗
Are you with me?
萨姆
Sam?
老天爷
Oh, gracious.
真见鬼 好多恶魔
Damn it. Demons.
全都是
All of them?
是福不是祸 是祸躲不过
No grass growing under your feet.
你有几把那种刀子
How many of those knives do you have?
只有一把
Just the one.
好吧 抱歉 我们现在怎么办
Well, then, forgive me, but what do we do?
是啊 迪恩
Yeah, Dean.
还有其他办法能搞定这么多恶魔吗
Got any other ideas how we could blast through that?
我们失陪一下
Excuse us.
梅格
Meg?
我勒个去啊…
Oh, for the love of…
萨姆在里头呢
Sam's in there.
我知道你与老友重逢不胜欢喜 但是
I know you're enjoying the double dip with your old pal, but …
你以为像你想的那么简单吗
You think it's that cut and dry?
真的吗
Really?
你知道他都干了什么
You know what he did.
你觉得你告诉他 他能像个没事人一样吗
And you want to tell him and just hope that he takes it in stride?
说不定他会崩溃 或者消失
He could snap. He could…disappear.
天知道
Who knows?
这么说我们认识
I gather we know each other.
不熟
Just a dollop.
告诉我吧 没事的
You can tell me. I'll be fine.
你怎么知道
How do you know?
你不了解自己 但我认识你很多年了
You just met yourself. I've known you for years.
你是个天使
You're an Angel.
抱歉 你是在挑逗我吗
I'm sorry? Is that a flirtation?
不 我说的是个物种
No, it's a species.
有强大的能力
A very powerful one.
她没说谎
She's not lying.
这就是你能治愈别人的原因
Okay? That's why you heal people.
还有你不吃东西
You don't eat.
你肯定还有其他特异功能
I'm sure there's more.
为什么不告诉我呢
Why wouldn't you tell me?
做个天使 听起来很好啊
Being an angel … it sounds pleasant.
一点也不好 相信我
It's not. Trust me.
血腥残杀 腐化堕落
It's bloody. It's corrupt.
一点也不好
It's not pleasant.
这些他都知道 你们曾并肩作战
He would know. You used to fight together.
都称得上是闺蜜了
Bestest friends, actually.
我们是朋友
We're…friends?
我是小卡吗
Am I Cass?
我完全没印象
I-I had no idea.
我不记得你了 对不起
I don't remember you. I'm sorry.
听着 你身怀神力
Look. You got the juice.
你能把那边的所有的恶魔都消灭
You can smite every demon in that lot.
但我不记得应该怎么做
But I don't remember how.
你有这能力
It's in there.
我相信就像骑自行车一样简单自如
I'm sure it's just like riding a bike.
可我也不知道怎么骑车啊
I don't know how to do that, either.
好吧 我会试试的
All right, I'll try.
这是行不通的
This ain't gonna go well.
我觉得说不定
I don't know.
我挺相信这小天使的
I believe in the little tree topper.
我认识你
Hey, I know you.
你已经死了
You're dead.
是啊 我也听说了
Yes, I've heard.
我很抱歉 迪恩
I'm sorry, Dean.
真是我的好小伙
That's my boy.
你跑也没有用的
I don't think running will save you.
干得漂亮 小天使
That was beautiful, Clarence.
小卡
Cass?
我记起你来了
I remember you.
我什么都记起来了
I remember everything.
我犯下的罪行
What I did.
我变成的怪物
What I became.
你怎么不告诉我
Why didn't you tell me?
因为萨姆在里面 就要死了
Because Sam is dying in there.
是我造成的
Because of me.
所有的一切
Everything.
死了这么多人都怪我
All these people.
我不该来这儿
I shouldn't be here.
小卡 小卡
Cass. Cass!
你待在这里
You stay here.
小卡
Cass!
这是
Where…
这里 这是哪里
Where … where are we?
电休克疗法治疗室
Electroshock therapy.
让我先把你安顿好
Let's just get you settled.
别害怕 这方法可帮了不少人
Don't be freaked. I've seen this help a lot of people.
我哥哥
My brother.
咬住
Bite down.
一般来说 使用的电流强度很低
Ordinarily, they keep this thing set on low.
但我想我们可以做点试验
But I was thinking we could experiment a little.
你觉得呢 萨姆
What do you say, Sam?
把头绑好
Let's get that head strapped in.
如果你还记得的话
If you remember,
那就该知道你当时已经极力挽救了
then you know you did the best you could at the time.
别为我辩解
Don't defend me.
你知道天堂里有多少人员伤亡吗
Do you have any idea the death toll in heaven?
人间又有多少
On Earth?
我们告别的时候很不愉快 迪恩
We didn't part friends, Dean.
那又如何
So what?
我死有应得
I deserved to die.
如果我不能挽救局面
Now, I can't possibly fix it…
又何必从那条河里走出来呢
So why did I even walk out of that river?
或许是为了挽救局面
Maybe to fix it.
等等
Wait.
真不可思议
Amazing.
你还真是能忍啊 伙计
You just take those lickin's, don't you, kid?
要是烤肉都能烤熟了
Well, if it's meat, you can cook it.
还得调大点火
You just got to turn up the heat.
我当初不应该摧毁你的屏障的 萨姆
I should never have broken your wall, Sam.
让我弥补自己的过失吧
I'm here to make it right.
你不是真实的
You're not real.
萨姆
Sam…
我很抱歉
…I'm so sorry.
第三只小猪很聪明嘛
I see that third little pig was smart.
出门找了点砖头来
Went out and got some bricks.
你说你做不到是什么意思
What the hell do you mean you can't?
就是说剩下的东西不足以重建屏障
I mean there's nothing left to rebuild.
为什么
Why not?
因为它崩塌了
Because it crumbled.
而他脑子里现在发生的一切
The pieces got crushed to dust.
把碎片都碾成渣了
by whatever's happening inside his head right now.
你是说没有别的法子了
So you're saying there's nothing?
他到死都是这幅鬼样子了
That he's gonna be like this until his candle blows out?
我很抱歉
I'm sorry.
我不能让这个问题消失
This isn't a problem I can make disappear.
你心里也清楚
And you know that.
但我也许可以将它转移
But I may be able to shift it.
转移
Shift?
是的 这可以让萨姆重新振作
Yeah, it would get Sam back on his feet.
这样会比较好
It's better this way.
我会没事的
I'll be fine.
等等 小卡 你要做什么
Wait, Cass, what are you doing?
萨姆
Now, Sam…
这可能会有点疼
This may hurt.
如果我没机会再对你说…
And if I can't tell you again…
我对我所做的深表抱歉
I'm sorry I ever did this to you.
萨姆
Sam?
- 迪恩 - 萨姆
- Dean! - Sam!
小卡
Cass?
小卡 是你吗
Cass, is that you?
你好啊 兄弟
Hello…Brother.
这不好吧
I don't know.
我们不能就这样丢下他
We can't just leave him.
我们不能带着他
Well, we can't bring him with us.
这世界上的妖魔鬼怪都在找我们
Everything on the planet's out for us, okay?
如果走漏了风声 我们可保护不了他
Word gets out, we can't protect him.
只能置他于险境
Not really.
这样安全点
This is safer.
所有知道小卡的事的恶魔都死绝了
Every demon who knows about Cass is dead.
还有没死的
Not everyone.
听着 迪恩 你这套
Look, Dean, this whole.
「敌人的敌人就是我的朋友」
"Enemy of my enemy is my friend" thing.
感觉就像个恶魔契约
feels kind of like a demon deal.
这不是个契约 这是
It's not a deal. It's …
是什么
It's what?
握着对方的致命把柄
Mutually assured destruction.
伙计 我明白 她不是我们的朋友
Look, man, I get it. She's not our friend.
我们没有朋友
We don't even have friends.
我们的朋友都死绝了
All our friends are dead.
看起来你资历很深
Well, you certainly have experience.
真不赖啊
I'm impressed.
告诉我
Tell me …
你为何想加入我们
why do you want to join our staff?
我只是想帮助患者
I really just want to help the patients.
照料他们
Watch over them.
不是我自夸
Not to be immodest,
但我觉得我能起很大作用
but I feel like I'd make a great fit.
我很同意
I can't argue with that.
欢迎加入我们
Welcome to the team…
马斯特斯护士
Nurse Masters.